<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<faq>
    <entry>
        <question>How did this get started?</question>
        <answer>Quidditch in its current form began at Middlebury college in 2005. From there, the sport spread like wild fire to campuses across the country and eventually the world, and the International Quidditch Association was born. Today, there are hundreds of active teams in more than 13 different countries.&#x3C;br/&#x3E;&#x3C;br/&#x3E;RIT Quidditch began in the fall of 2009. Since those early days playing with make shift hoops and dollar store supplies, we have become an official RIT club and continue to grow in size and recognition.</answer>

    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>How can you play Quidditch?</question>
        <answer>Obviously being incapable of flight, our version of the game is kept to the ground. All though it lacks high flying adventure, Quidditch is a physically intense, full contact sport.  The four positions of the fictional game are all included, all though they have been adapted to exist in our so called "reality".</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>What do Chasers do?</question>
        <answer>Chasers are the main scoring position. Chasers work together to move the Quaffle ball down field and score on the opposing team's goal, while at the same time defending against attacks from the other team. Each team has three Chasers.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>What do Beaters do?</question>
        <answer>Beaters are the source of havoc on the pitch. A beater's job is to use a Bludger ball to knock opposing players temporarily out of play. A knocked out player must return to their goals before being able to return to the game. Each team has two beaters, and there are three Bludgers on the field at a time.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>What do Keepers do?</question>
        <answer>A Keeper's main job is to defend their goal against the other team. Within the keeper-zone, a special area surrounding their goals, a keeper can not be knocked out by Bludgers or tackled by opposing players. Outside of the keeper-zone, they act as Chasers for power-plays against their unsuspecting adversaries! Each team has one keeper.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>What do Seekers do?</question>
        <answer>A Seeker's job is the most straight forward of all positions: to catch the snitch! Catching the snitch awards extra points to the seeker's team and ends the game. Finding and catching the snitch is task of incredible difficulty, as the snitch knows few rules in preventing itself from getting caught.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>How does the snitch work?</question>
        <answer>As much a crowd pleaser as part of the game, the snitch consists of a ball attached to a runner. It is the runner's job to make sure, by any means, to keep the seekers from grabbing the ball attached to them. And by any means, we mean anything: Utilizing cars, climbing trees and stealing other balls are all completely legal.</answer>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <question>Can I play?</question>
        <answer>Of course! Anyone is free to show up at our regular meet ups/practices. Just check the our calendar for our meeting schedule.</answer>
    </entry>
</faq>
